{"data":[{"question":"Sometimes, ___ should be strict with ___.","a":"the teacher, students","b":"teacher, a student","c":"teachers, a student","d":"teachers, students","answer":"4","explain":"\n- This is general speaking case= don't use article with nouns","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"An ant has two ___ in its body.","a":"stomachs","b":"stomaches","c":"stomacks","d":"stomackes","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- \"Stomachs\" is plural of \"stomach\"\n\n","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"They played on the ___ for half an hour, and when they returned they found their goods ___ stolen.","a":"sand, was","b":"sand, were","c":"sands, was","d":"sands, were","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Sand: uncountable noun \n- Goods: plural","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"It's bad ___ to speak with your mouth full of food.","a":"manner's","b":"manner","c":"manners'","d":"manners","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- We say \" have good\/bad manners\"","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"There is a large ___ that needs harvesting.","a":"number of wheats","b":"number of wheat","c":"amount of wheats","d":"amount of wheat","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Wheat: unaccountable noun\n\n- Number of: use with countable noun\n\n- Amount of : mostly use with uncountable noun","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"As a teacher she is ___. But as a writer she is ___.","a":"success, failure","b":"a success, a failure","c":"success, a failure","d":"a success, failure","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Be a success\/ failure as a ... (=be successful\/unsuccessful in a particular job)","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"What ___ is the cake? It's round.","a":"shape","b":"area","c":"type","d":"size","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Round-> What + shape","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"The nurse forgot to tell the patient how many ___ he should pay for pulling out the tooth.","a":"costs","b":"money","c":"pays","d":"dollars","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Cost, money, pay: uncoutable noun\n\n- Dollar: countable noun","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"Who did you spend last Sunday with? \" ___ .\"","a":"The Palmer's","b":"Palmer's","c":"The Palmers'","d":"The Palmers","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- When a family name (a proper noun) is pluralized, we almost always simply add an \"s.\"\n\n- Do not form a family name plural by using an apostrophe; that device is reserved for creating possessive forms.","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"Being able to speak as many languages as you can is a great ___ when you're looking for a job.","a":"chance","b":"advantage","c":"importance","d":"assistant","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- We offen say  \"great\/big\/considerable advantage\"\n\n- Meaning of advantage is most suitable in this case","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"}]}